<resources>
   <string name="app_name">Test Application</string>
   <string name="hint_id">Enter ID number</string>
   <string name="button_text">Button</string>
   <string name="classes_prompt">Choose a class</string>
   <string name="name300">Major ProSeminar</string>
   <string name="name311">Intro to Computer Networks</string>
   <string name="name325">Graphics Programming</string>
   <string name="name334">Operating Systems</string>
   <string name="name336">Internet Programming</string>
   <string name="name338">Software Design</string>
   <string name="name363">Introduction to Database Systems</string>
   <string name="name370">Design and Analysis of Algorithms</string>
   <string name="name383">Introduction to Data Science</string>
   <string name="desc300">Helps students identify and articulate personal, professional, and social
        goals. Provides an integrated overview of the computer science and communication design
        majors and their requirements. Students develop a plan for their learning goals. Students
        learn writing, presentation, research and critical-thinking skills within the diversified
        fields of information technology and communication design. Students learn how to analyze,
        predict, and articulate trends in the academic, public service</string>
   <string name="desc311">Survey of Telecomm and Data Comm Technology Fundamentals, Local Area
        Network, Wide Area Network, Internet and internetworking protocols including TCP/IP, network
        security and performance, emerging industry trends such as voice over the network and high
        speed networking. Designed as a foundation for students who wish to pursue more advanced
        network studies including certificate programs. Includes hands-on networking labs that
        incorporate Cisco CCNA lab components.</string>
   <string name="desc325">This course teaches the students the fundamentals of game programming and
        skills needed for game development, including GPU programming, matrix and quaternion algebra
        for physics calculation, animation, lighting and basics of implementing 3D models into a
        framework.</string>
   <string name="desc334">Students in this course will learn about the use and design of modern
        operating systems, focusing on Linux. On the “use” side, students will learn the Linux
        command line, to write shell scripts, and to build programs with GNU utilities like awk,
        sed, and make. On the “design” side, students will develop a deep understanding of process
        management, memory management, file systems, and concurrency, and how they apply to modern
        technologies like virtualization and cloud computing.</string>
   <string name="desc336">Provides students with dynamic web application development skills,
        focusing on the integration of server-side programming, database connectivity, and
        client-side scripting. Coverage includes the Internet architecture, responsive design,
        RESTful web services, and Web APIs.</string>
   <string name="desc338">Provides students with the fundamental concepts to develop large-scale
        software, focusing on the object-oriented programming techniques. Coverage includes the
        introduction to Java programming language, object-oriented programming, software life cycle
        and development processes, requirements analysis, and graphical user interface
        development.</string>
   <string name="desc363">This course provides balanced coverage of database use and design,
        focusing on relational databases. Students will learn to design relational schemas, write
        SQL queries, access a DB programmatically,and perform database administration. Students
        will gain a working knowledge of the algorithms and data structures used in query
        evaluation and transaction processing. Students will also learn to apply newer database
        technologies such as XML, NoSQL, and Hadoop.</string>
   <string name="desc370">Students learn important data structures in computer science and acquire
        fundamental algorithm design techniques to get the efficient solutions to several computing
        problems from various disciplines. Topics include the analysis of algorithm efficiency,
        hash, heap, graph, tree, sorting and searching, brute force, divide-and-conquer,
        decrease-and-conquer, transform-and-conquer, dynamic programming, and greedy
        programming.</string>
   <string name="desc383">In data science, data analysis and machine learning techniques are
        applied to visualize data, understand trends, and make predictions. In this course students
        will learn how to obtain data, preprocess it, apply machine learning methods, and visualize
        the results. A student who completes the course will have enough theoretical knowledge, and
        enough skill with modern statistical programming languages and their libraries,to define
        and perform complete data science projects.</string>
</resources>
